const STORE = [
  {
  question: "Who starred as 'Neo' in the Matrix Trilogy?",
  answers:[
    "Peter Dinklage",
    "Eminem",
    "Keanu Reeves",
    "Justin Timberlake"
  ],
  correct: "Keanu Reeves"
},
{
  question: "What voice actor portrayed the character 'The Donkey' in the Shrek movies?",
  answers:[
    "John Snow",
    "Will Smith",
    "Arnold Schwarzenegger",
    "Eddie Murphy"
  ],
  correct:"Eddie Murphy"
},
{
  question: "In the movie series Mission Impossible, what agency does Ethan Hunt work for?",
  answers:[
    "MI-5",
    "MIB",
    "MI-6",
    "FBI"
  ],
  correct:"MI-6"
},
{
  question: "What is the name of the character portrayed by Vin Diesel in the movie 'Riddik'? ",
  answers:[
    "Riddik",
    "Captain Jack Sparrow",
    "Nemo",
    "Darth Maul"
  ],
  correct:"Riddik"
},
{
  question: "Who directed the movie 'Hateful 8'?",
  answers:[
    "Peter Jackson",
    "Quentin Tarantino",
    "Jack Black",
    "Michael Jackson"
  ],
  correct:"Quentin Tarantino"
},
{
  question: "Harry Potter is a?",
  answers:[
    "Wizard",
    "Space Ship",
    "Sith Lord",
    "Super Saiyan"
  ],
  correct:"Wizard"
},
{
  question: "'You are terminated!' Is a popular quote from which movie?",
  answers:[
    "Fast and the Furious",
    "The Avengers",
    "The Terminator",
    "Shrek"
  ],
  correct:"The Terminator"
},
{
  question: "What is the name of the Hobbit, played by Elijah Wood, in the Lord of the Rings movies",
  answers:[
    "Johnny Depp",
    "Bagginhasin Frododo",
    "Frodu McBaggins",
    "Frodo Baggins"
  ],
  correct:"Frodo Baggins"
},
{
  question: "'No, I am your Father' is a popular quote from which movie?",
  answers:[
    "Avatar",
    "Star Wars",
    "Jurassic Park",
    "John Wick"
  ],
  correct:"Star Wars"
},
{
  question: "Who is the best Super Hero?",
  answers:[
    "Iron Man",
    "Iron Man",
    "Iron Man",
    "Iron Man"
  ],
  correct:"Iron Man"
},

]
